

### PROFILE BRIEF

### SHRIJITH KRISHNAN

Professional with 18 years of Sales Experience in Jobs and EdTech Domain.Penchant for delivering results.

Instrumental in establishing successful EdTech vertical, played pivotal role in the growth story of Leading Internet and E-Learning companies.

Energised by new challenges. Proven track record in EdTech Sales, Leadership, Strategy Formulation, Growth Mapping, Business Expansion, Team Management. Life Long Learner.

### Contact Info



9849695326



Hyderabad,Telangana



shrijithk@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/shrijith-krishnan-a90b1a13/

#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Learning Agility | Start-up Experience | Decision Making Business Growth & Forecasting | Strategy | People Management Resource Planning | Problem Solving | Driving Performance

#### PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

VICE PRESIDENT & NATIONAL HEAD | JAN 2021-PRESENT CORPORATE GURUKUL LEARNING PVT LTD.

- Spearheading National Edu-Sales
- Growth Hacking
- Envisaging business opportunities and working on robust sales process
- Implementing strategies to augment business and promote products for business excellence
- Develop GTM strategies for Business Expansion
- Building high performance teams

### AVP-SALES | JUNE 2016 - DECEMBER-2020 INFO EDGE INDIA LTD (SHIKSHA)

- Heading Education Sales.
- Aligning Region's Growth and Performance
- with Business Targets.
- Capacity building and Scale Appreciation
- appreciation.
- Building Effective Teams
- Stakeholder Management.
- Client Connect and Revenue Generation.

# SR.ZONAL MANAGER | MAY 2014 - MAY 2016 INFO EDGE INDIA LTD (SHIKSHA)

- Heading Education Sales function in South.
- Business Growth | New Client Acquisition
- Focus on Team Building | Team L&D
- Client Engagement & Revenue growth

.

# ZONAL MANAGER | MAY 2012 - MAY 2014 INFO EDGE INDIA LTD (SHIKSHA)

- Scaling Shiksha Business
- Consolidating leadership Position of the business through Customer Initiatives
- Business Strategy Formulation
- Client Engagement | Talent Acquisition
- Team Management | Team Enrichment | Market Research,

# BRANCH MANAGER | MAY 2008 - MAY 2012 INFO EDGE INDIA LTD (SHIKSHA)

- Established Shiksha Business,
- Business Strategy design
- Client Acquisition, Talent Acquisition, Team
- Management, Market Research,
- EducationalLeadership | Leadership Development,

# SR. EXEC -AREA MANAGER | JAN 2004- APRIL 2008 INFO EDGE INDIA LTD (NAUKRI.COM)

- Played vital role in setting up Naukri Business in the region.
- Handled end to end sales function client mapping, campaign, Management, business development, team handling, hiring.
- Achieved synergy between Business Growth and Customer Expectation

#### MILESTONES

- Managed & Scaled Startup Business at Pan India Level.
- Established Shiksha Business as the leading force in the Education space..
- Established Naukri as the No.1 Player in the region.
- Consistently Rated as Top Performing Manager
- Led Best Performing Team, Nationally (3 years in a row)

#### CERTIFICATIONS

- Communicate to Influence [Linkedin]
- Leading Strategically [Linkedin]
- Mindsets and Strategies for Negotiation Success [Linkedin]
- Leading with a Growth Mindset [Linkedin]
- Leadership Mindsets [Linkedin]
- Creating a Culture of Strategy Execution [Linkedin]

#### EDUCATION

- INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY AND MARKETING(ITM)
  PGDM (MARKETING)-2002-04
- CALICUT UNIVERSITY-KERALA
  BACHELORS IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION 1999-2002
- ST. ANSELMS SR. SECONDARY SCHOOL-RAJASTHAN